# OGUNMISI OLUWASEUN

No 3A, Road 61, Victoria Garden City, Lekki, Lagos State

**Mobile**: 08035422821

**Email**: ogunmisi\_oluwaseun@yahoo.com

Marital Status: Single

**Religion:** Christianity

Sex: Male

## STATEMENT OF OBJECTIVE

Flexibleand verse individual with advanced knowledge of administrative ethics, human resource principles and ability to professionally handle assignments in different fields. The combination of the experience I have got from the positions I have held has helped me in broadening my horizon and has quipped me with a ground knowledge to work with different organizations, more so, affords my potential employer the flexibility to place me in a broad range of demanding situations, with confidence that I will undertake my duties professionally effectively.

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND WITH DATES:**

2010- 2014 University of Ilorin, Ilorin, (B.A Linguistics).

**2005** West African Senior School Certificate Examination.

**1997 – 2003** Aquinas College, Akure, Ondo State, (SSCE).

# ADDITIONAL PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION WITH DATES:

2015 Human Resource Management.

2015 Business Analysis.

2015 National Youth Service Corps.

**2015** Certificate of Participation, (FRSC Special Marshal).

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE:**

2012-2013

**Employer:** Alcatel Lucent, Victoria Island, Lagos.

**Position:** Contract Staff.

**Responsibilities:** Inspection and monitoring of Etisalat sites in Osun State.

2013-2015

**Employer:** Water view Hotel and Resorts

**Position:** Supervisor

**Employer**: Spring Aluminum, Ilorin Branch.

**Position**: Marketing Manager.

**Responsibilities**: Designing strategies on how customers and clients can be brought to the company. Mapping out ways the clients can be kept. Doing different market analysis. Keeping ahead of our major competitors etc.

October, 2015 to September, 2017

**Employer:** Micjosh Global Resources Ltd, Akobo, Ibadan.

**Position**: GeneralManager.

Responsibilities: Overseeing department functions and managing

employees,

developing strategic solutions to meet workforce demands and labour force trendscoupled with hiring of

workforce.

**Employer:** College of Education, IkereEkiti, Ekiti State. **Position:** Coordinator, Ilorin Study Centre (On contract).

Responsibilities: Management of the students and members of staff.

September, 2017 till Date

**Employer**: Hugotaxi Technology, No4, Babatope Bejide Crescent,

Lekki Phase 1

**Position**: Manager.

Responsibilities: Decision making, Overseeing department functions and

managing employees, developing strategic solutions to meet workforce demands and labour force trends

coupled with hiring of work force.

**PUBLICATIONS:** 

Language Endangerment, A Case Study of Okeagbe-Akoko. General English (GNS 111), College of Education Ikere-Ekiti, Ekiti State.

## **SKILLS/ATTRIBUTES:**

Integrity, highly focused, reliable,good humanrelation, good communication and adaptability.

#### **COMPUTER LITERACY:**

Proficient in the use of Microsoft office application such as Microsoft Office word, Page Maker, Microsoft Excel.

#### **INTEREST/ACTIVITIES:**

Reading, research, modifying my environment and motivating people.

# LINGUISTIC COMPETENCE:

English language and Yoruba language.

#### **REFEREES:**

# DR OTUN-FRIDAY,

Head of Department, Department of Linguistics, University of Ilorin. 07065164064.

## **ENG. MICHAEL BOROKINI**

Managing Director, Micjosh Global Resources Limited, TomatPlaza,Elewuro B/Stop, Akobo, Ibadan. 080-591-90248.

## **JAMES CLASSPETERS**

Partner Manager Hugotaxi Technology . 0802 222 6365.